Semih GOKCEOGLU

125 Parkway Forest Dr, North York, ON M2J 1L9, Canada 6477674910

semih.gkcoglu@gmail.com

Technical Skills

Likes:

node.js, extjs, express, mongodb, jquery, nodejs, asp.net, c#, java, angularjs, c++, obj-c, php, html, javascript, android, redis, wordpress, magento, gulp, nightwatch.js, expressjs, asynchrounous, parallel, programming, opencv, andengine, git, bower, svn, socket.io, web, socket, heroku

Dislikes: php

Experience

Full Stack Developer - Heliocentris - Agri-T

April 2015 - Current

mongodb, angularjs, extjs, node.js, magento, sencha-touch, socket.io

I have been working as a Full Stack Developer in this company since April 2015. Within this period, I have attended many crucial projects include ERP and commercial apps for telecommincation companes. I mainly have used nodejs, mongodb, exts, angularjs as MEAN stack.

Full Stack Developer - Verisan

January 2015 - April 2015

angularjs, c#, rest, html, css

Developed, tested and implemented web applications using MS SQL, Angular Js/ ASP.NET. Focused on web service (REST, JSON) integration based on client/server network architecture.

Computer Science Internship - Turk Telekom

May 2013 - August 2013

asp.net, mysql, c#

Focused on IP/MPLS, IPTV and IPv6 transition methods. Created online system for the Network Department of the Turk Telekom. Created requirement and specification document, design, architecture and dependency model for provisioning work-order tracking system.

Software Internship - ELMED

June 2012 - August 2012

c#, asp.net

Designed and developed software for the Uroflowmetry. Demonstrated simultaneous measurement between device and API. Attended corporate training seminars.

Education

Post Graduate Certificate - Mobile Application Development - Lambton College

2016

swift, java, android, ios

I have a strong passion improving my skills on mobile development. So, I came to study mobile application development.

Bachelor of Science Computer Engineering – Gazi University

2009 - 2014

Algorithm and main code structure were gained properly.

High School of Science - Ozgoren

2005 - 2009

Projects & Interests

GitHub - Buffly - https://github.com/SemihGk/Buffly

June 2016

simple chat web and ios application

GitHub - CrudApp - https://github.com/SemihGk/CrudApp

May 2016

simple swift application

GitHub - resumeApp - https://github.com/SemihGk/resumeApp

June 2016

resume application

Tools

First Computer: Favorite Editor: MAC OS Atom

Background

My Weaknesses

I only have 20 hours work permit per week (legally). But it does not mean I will limit myself with 20 hours. I do not have excellent verbal or writing communication skills. But I can explain myself very well. I do not prefer PHP at back-end. I had experienced some troubles in the past. Using magento for a while and I was really sick and tired with PHP My current focus is mobile development. So, I also want to improve myself in mobile area. As you may notice, I have been studying mobile application development and I want to be expert in mobile and web apps. I

have classes in week days.But my classes start 6 pm. So, I am suitable for full time job position.

My Aims

I have been improving myself in web and mobile applications for 3-4 years and want to be expert in this fields Following and learning new technologies in my country is a little bit hard. So, I came here and I am so eager to learn new skills Since I came to Toronto, I could not find any programmer friend and I missed to work in an office environment.

My some skills you might like

Quick adaptation, strong passion being successful, very well organized while coding, working with any field and full-focus on my job.

Note Unfortunately, I cannot add my projects' links into my resume since all of them are ERP applications. But I would like to show them on online presentation or at a meeting.

References:

My project manager: Baris Cicek -> barisc@yandex.com

My college teacher: Pedram Faghihi -> pedram.faghihi@gmail.com